good morning welcome to day 34
possibility during the pandemic
today is Sunday so I am telling a story
of which of course it's not going to
follow a linear sequence although I did
write it down Leonard Leonard a little
bit your sequence so I didn't really
plan before the day of what it is we're
talking about and today because it's
Sunday story time and I talked to the
last week there was one about my sister
what about my brain my sister wasn't
last week was it because that seems like
centuries oh but maybe maybe west last
week but today we're going to talk about
marijuana because I am it's a thing it's
a thing in my life
and why not um tell that story and then
I had to remember what the first time I
smoked pot was and I couldn't remember
when I did it I was like how did I
possibly forget that I was visiting I
was sixteen visiting one of my best
friends from grade six school year in
Calgary I lived in Lethbridge those two
hours away my mom was dating or married
to she'd eventually married the guy and
so this guy who I hate that's not the
point not the point of this story his
sister was in a and and her husband and
so was my best friend's mom and so they
all became friends so my future step
cousin and me and my best friend I don't
even know where we got the pot from but
guarantee you they had it you'll have 45
minutes or left brain and she I grew up
in left bridge I went to Winston
Churchill High School and so we got pot
and we smoked it we must have smoked it
four or five times that day and it never
actually took like it never hello your
name's also Mary Jane so this is your
table okay um periscope which I forget
I'm also on youtube so so people know
what what we're talking about and I put
up the wrong comments about that onion
huh 40 minutes from bridge and so I
didn't get the effects of marijuana of
the pot that we smoked again and again
they it was definitely neither of their
first
it was my first time though and then
that evening we smoked we walked to the
park that was three blocks from her
house and we smoked it and it's like the
whole days marijuana hit me all at once
I've never been that that high that like
hallucinogenic high on marijuana ever
since but I remember walking we smoked
it walked to the park smoked it again
and it's like I walked back in a
different world and right face but like
a yin-yang and he we were this it was a
weird night and our I think my parents
were at night meeting I don't even know
where our parents were my mom possibly
was fucking love bridge with her husband
or boyfriend at the time again I don't
oh we got married they got my regret for
my grade 12th year so they weren't
married yet but they may have been
engaged so that was my my first time
with pot during high school I didn't
smoke it chronically because I grew up
somewhere where it was illegal and I
never bought it I actually never bought
pot my on my own until I was in my 30s
so I only ever smoked it when it was
available I don't I don't I have these
weird things in my life where that when
I go a long time without doing it it
becomes part of my identity a bit of
like I couldn't possibly because I don't
do that it's like I don't smoke I don't
buy it I just look it when it's
available if I bought it that would be a
problem they dyed my hair I've never
dyed my hair and now that I've never
dyed my hair and I'm 40 I couldn't
possibly but so um where are we
what high school smoked it sure and
recreationally any time I smoked a lot
of times there was alcohol involves and
I would end up throwing up but I did
enjoy it and I when it was available one
of my best friends the one who made the
necklace was a pot smoker and so when we
would hang out we would smoke pot but it
was just that I was hanging out with
friends and then I moved from Alberta
which is very alcohol not but they don't
tell us to do drugs but to BC which is
even more Pro marijuana I ended up
working at Starbucks a few blocks from
my house and I ended up dating one of my
co-workers who also happened to work
there basically from what I understand
years later as a pot dealer like he
didn't he wasn't there for the minimum
wage
Starbucks job he was there suppose
customers
could come and he could hide it between
the like tall I think he figure out a
system would tweet like he put a tall
cup and a grande cup and he'd hide
underneath he lived in the ability
upstairs which in downtown Vancouver is
it expensive building and he had this I
don't know he grew up rich in north van
and he had this chip on his shoulder
about it he oh god I want to say its
name but we're still we're still friends
you know acquaintances yours years later
but the our whole relationship was
hilarious maybe that'll be its own story
time I'll go through all of my exes but
which there aren't that many of them
which is funny goodness Sunday in
sniping but he was a pot dealer here not
moving in with one of these other guys
who I think was also made me a pot
dealer but because he was a pot dealer
basically he had he had a little extra
money he seemed to think anyway he grew
up rich and then he had this like chip
on his shoulder I remember one time
we're all working at Starbucks we're all
minimum-wage workers and we were going
on a party we were going to a party that
wasn't downtown and so we took the bus
instead of taking taxis were like 18 19
20 year olds and he's like oh my god my
friends might see me on the bus which
years later is a freaking hilarious
because although there was a stigma in
like Lethbridge growing up if you took
the bus because mainly your parents
drove you around and the bus system was
so shit everybody here takes the bus I'd
have millionaire friends who take this
guy train downtown if there's a hockey
game because just easier so the fact
that anyway getting on the sidetrack
about about him but his but he is like
he's intertwined with of course my love
life because he's max but also like my
marijuana wife he because he was a
dealer because we had pot all the time
and we smoked pot a lot and then when
one of our friends from from Starbucks
also was over a lot smoking pot one of
the older older guys who who worked at
Starbucks still friends with all these
people so I still know them so when I
give their exact name but he we OH after
we broke up he went and moved moved just
immigrated to Israel joined the army
took her video room at middle school
he's
by now and uh but right after we broke
up he opens a pot-smoking store down on
where pot-smoking stores are in
Vancouver it was open for like three
months no one knows what it is it had a
horrible name and he was just smoking
pot is very intimately intertwined with
him especially since years later when he
came back to visit we smoked pot he
heard all this like weird trek through
where we were like rock climbing without
any gear he was gonna like hit a dog
with a two-by-four cuz he's terrified of
dogs he had a scar on his face when he
was attacked he was like - and we were
trying to get away we were like walking
through people's yards a North Vancouver
that was along the water and this is not
not not the point not the point at all
we got high we walked to the beach we
had some adventures and then as long
after we broke up what was my point of
that though that Oh even even as a rabbi
even as two decades later he still
smokes pot daily it's still very much a
part of his of his spiritual journey
every day and I think yeah I would say I
was judgmental about him for that now he
would say I'm in the same category so
then it's funny how it's so intertwined
with what it must have been after so
yeah after we broke up and I was living
downtown my my sister was living with
her boyfriend in a house that grew pot
that was his thing that he did is he
grew pot he's one of my favor my I hate
all of my sisters boyfriends he's one of
the only ones that I actually like he's
a good guy and but anyway we to pay the
rent we grew pot in the basement but it
was this big secret so I'm working at
Starbucks I can't have anyone drop me
off
nobody's allowed to know where I live I
ended up dating um I ever tell dating
story one of my best friends from back
in Alberta's brothers and he came to
visit and he knew that we lived in a
grow house if my sister didn't know that
he knew we lived in her house so I had
to like hide it from him and then they
were out I showed him the thing
downstairs is like 20 years ago so it's
not it's statute of limitations as well
as personal thoughts legal here now but
it wasn't legal here then and there was
this one particular time we lived in
in our house or we grew pot and we cut
it down every six weeks to eight months
to eight points to eight weeks we would
we would cut it down it would take a
weekend to cut it music on and cut all
the the pot plants and that was
basically paying rent and then I paid my
sister like fifty five hundred bucks a
month for food and I lived there
rent-free if you can call cutting down
plants for for 48 hours rent-free every
eight six to eight weeks but there was
this one point her boyfriend had another
grow house that he had with some friends
and we went over there to to help him
cut it down because he couldn't get any
workers and on the way back so there's
me my sister who's like blond him who's
like a white Alberta boy but we're
driving in his in his truck we just cut
down six weeks worth of pot it's in the
back of the truck we're we've been
drinking so like we we were drinking a
couple drinks so he maybe was like it's
slightly over or slightly under the
legal limit for her alcohol in his
system we got stopped by the cops
because he was speeding and the three
white kids just got to be like they were
like yeah don't have you been drinking
yeah just one just I'm just I just
picked them up cuz they were drinking
and I'm just their designated driver I
had one at home and I came to get them
luckily they never looked at the the
back part because otherwise we all would
have criminal records we skated by and
it's one of my closest brushes with the
law where I was doing something illegal
and got away with it even though I was
it like someone a by standard I wasn't
my house I was I'm just helping out but
I still would have could it would have
could have gotten a criminal record and
they're not yeah once you have a
criminal record it's hard to rid of
so that was my period I thought I could
calm down with this story hour because I
don't really need to tell it was like
how did you got it through why did you
go through it you needed it up to today
with marijuana
so anyway chancara house i right after
living there went to west wing Costa
Rica Costa Rica to volunteer and then
came back when came back was living with
my friends who don't smoke pot they knew
we had lived in a
I was trying to put this together my
Swiss cheese brain came back from
Australia and my brother had moved here
and all three of us lived in a grow
house mr. sunder that was a good way to
pay the rent had this whole moving from
there not moving from that house to the
next house we lived in was a whole
fiasco all of my moves but you know the
whole story story Sunday on all of the
moves that I've had and especially those
two moves one move that house like I saw
someone jump off a bridge my sister
really caught in an accident with one of
the city buses with the u-haul there was
like no light we were moving all night
we hadn't rolling the couch across we'd
grass stains on it
they broke the TV good times good times
I don't think we probably weren't
smoking pot we were moving my sister
wouldn't even if she was driving my
brother and I it's weird cuz we had a
ton of pot like a lot cuz we lived in a
grow house and at the same time I don't
think I smoked it anywhere near as much
as I smoke no I know I didn't eat spoken
in here as you know and so we moved to
another house which theoretically were
gonna set up as a girl house and then
didn't because I don't actually remember
why my sister moved to LA but that
wasn't why she was gonna do that anyway
I think the house didn't work out and
then it was too much of a hassle so we
ended up I ended up just finding a house
I didn't really want her house anymore
too much drama and secrecy and the one
we had lived in first it was a very
professional setup let's say the second
one we lived in on the North Shore
was like a fire hazard whenever we're an
ex-boyfriend who actually really
disliked was the one who set that one up
and he's one of those people like Trump
who's an overestimate or like I could do
this the other guy I don't think he had
electricians degree but he knew how to
set it up it is it's what he did instead
of just stepping into it I'm thinking
you can do it anyway so Oh late with so
my brother and I lived together my
sister moved didn't smoke a lot of pot
besides what we had I think again when
his and had one of his his old friends
from Alberta moved in I think he smoked
pot so you know
three of us smoked pot together then my
I moved out I was like okay it's finally
it's time to stop living with siblings
or my brother probably decided that
actually he moved out on his own I found
a different place with my with my friend
who lived here the necklace died and we
lived together a very short period of
time before I had brain tumors he had a
pot addiction and he would be like you
you take my pot and I'll ask you for it
when I wanted and was addicted to it he
had some some issues with that but I
still didn't even after I had my brain
surgery I remember when I was in my my
brain was swelling and I was throwing
tantrums and someone had to go and get
pot for me it was like my mom or someone
who'd obviously does not smoke pot I
mean it's just my mom was there I would
have smoked erics that doesn't make any
sense I smoked Derek's pot well I
wouldn't know if he's in the house that
makes sense but my mom was there while I
was smoking it was the first time I ever
smoked in front of my mom and I wanted
something but I wasn't doing it besides
that one time so I wasn't doing it
around my brain surgery it was just like
that at one time I think it was to try
it to see if it helped with my pretty
much moment we didn't know that yet but
but hey why not bring down some
inflammation so then and also I was
working in a lab at the time and we
definitely like went down to wreck beach
it smoked pot with it allowed people but
it wasn't a daily thing it was like
every few weeks we probably went down
drug beach art so much smoke pot smoking
pot and talking biology math was very
conducive I think we didn't smoke in
science one but we when we went on on
our few weekends that we went away for
and when there was a drinky and it was
like people would get drunk and then do
math proofs on the board this is what
geeks do when they're cool awesome
I don't know how to follow this but
there's something about it that was
really cool so then half my search I
remember right after my surgery not
wanting to have any kind of alcohol or
drugs it was like my body was reboard
and it was like I'm as a child but in a
really weird like I didn't crave it it
wasn't trying not to do it it was just
it was weird I was like alcohol and then
after a few months that went away and
then I was back to I'm never drinking
that much because great for me but
pot pot I hope July Oh with mist
we missed because I know working a lab
had brain surgery did that so then I
dated this guy who were still really
good friends his name just because it's
easier with the name is Ian and we lived
together we dated for like three years
we lived together for about two of those
years he moved when we moved out from
with each other we broke up because I
wanted a kid and he didn't he moved in
with a roommate who became his life and
I moved into here and have had various
roommates in this place since then so
it's had my and my baby my permanent
roommate after that so having um I know
me live together we were really not
compatible in marijuana why is because
he was someone who always needed it in
the house but you could go days without
smoking it and I'm someone who can go
without it in the house but if it's in
the house I need to smoke it and so as
Mataji in our addictions together it was
like just broken because I'd be like I'd
have to be like hey pretend it's not in
the house and so even though he would
never go for a walk I'd be like I'm
going for a walk like I don't know what
he's doing cool have fun outside and so
he'd be smoking it when I was on periods
of time if not smoking it and then when
we broke up he went off of it for a
while I'm pretty sure he's 99% Sur him
and him and his his wife smoking no but
there was a period term we went off it I
also didn't really I wasn't smoking it
either cuz he was I had guys so until we
broke up I hadn't bought pot it's still
up to that point in my life I'd never
purchased it which is sure to post up a
freeloader more than anything I'd bought
alcohol I'd probably even bought
mushrooms but I hadn't and I think I put
money into my pot but I hadn't like gone
to buy it and one of our friends
actually though I met him he is a pot
dealer and so I ended up buying through
her and I bought for her for four years
and we're still friends and I still
sometimes buy through her but I have my
different a different source now so I
would go out of my way every couple
months to go buy it from her I buy my
stockpile but then I know I was gonna
have a baby I was trying to have a baby
so I stopped smoking pot for a while and
like you're supposed to go off in it for
like a year before you smoked pot
otherwise there's this tiny increased
chance of a heart defect
but other than that if you're not gonna
go out for six months it's basically
useless and basically somewhat a lot of
the tests have shown that it's okay to
smoke during pregnancy like again the
problem is go off for six months you
don't get this birth defect or it
actually has very little impact they've
tried to study it they've studied it
tried to find negative impacts and it
actually showed the opposite that they
tried to do a long-term study of mothers
who smoked pot while they were pregnant
and it's this is I I have to actually
get to this federal offense it's just an
old wives tale
but in besides community these things
often pan out to be true that they were
trying to a long term sorry marijuana
with with mothers who were smoking it
showed it the five-year mark that the
kids were actually smarter than the ones
who had he smoked pot so they terminated
the study they were like oh we can't
showcase that he's like well anyway well
I was pregnant very pregnant my again
I've had a lot of roommates living here
I like had my donor company an aged
owner come and stay with me we conceived
here was a whole whole thing I loved
that's why yeah
you
back kid needed hairbrush something like
the drawers like for reason why she's in
here naked gone broad scrambled to not
let that happen so I was living here
had a roommate who knew that that was
what I was doing she moved in but she
didn't want to come and live here the
year after she had school during the
she's quit EU BC and then when she got
out for the spring for spring and was
gonna go home to Alberta for the summer
and then come back he decided she went
to live residence so the next roommate I
found was one of the there's only two
roommates that I've kicked out that I've
said actually we're not compatible once
they've moved in she was one of them and
right after she moved in she was just
like she's like you don't have a
microwave I wanna I want to read
discount you notice how I ended up
anywhere she was she was a nightmare and
mmm what he's worked compatible really
but right after she moved in there was
somebody in this neighborhood who was
looking for a place and she was a single
mom and an amazing human being and she
ended up moving in well I was pregnant
she's like a vegan Rastafari and she had
a four-year-old daughter and so this is
irony that so my brother at the time was
dating this woman who he was basically
the father of her her son like once they
started dating the son was too and he
basically became a father to him when
they broke up she gave custody to the
bio dad and my dad my brother has the
same sense but at the time he was my
nephew and it was funny because I was he
was the same age as this little girl I
was living with and I would talk about
pot in front of my brother and his
girlfriend who smoking and they'd be
like you can't say it in front of the
Sun because he'll go to the dad and say
have no get in trouble and I was like oh
families because the four-year-old
I live with is fake rolling joints as
like a tea party it's basically her tea
party because her mom's Rastafari and
her dad's rest Aparri and her
grandmother on her grandmother on her
dad side her dad's Jamaican and on that
side all of her family smokes pot and on
her other side from on the side
her mom's converted Rastafarian hippie
totally smokes pot her grandpa's a sari
for grandpa on her mom's side is a
hippie and smokes pot and her mom
all of them smoke and she like rolls
joins as like it's a tea party right
it's just part of life it's like
communion as a kid and so the did the
dichotomous difference between like the
four-year-old bits my nephew and I we
can't talk about it in front of him it's
like it doesn't exist even though we're
rolling it going outside and smoking it
versus this little four-year-old that I
live with
anyway she ended up her parents lived a
few blocks away I still walk by their
house constantly and she lived here but
it was hard to share a room with the kid
and she end up moving back in with her
parents and right before I gave birth
and because she had she's going back to
another parent she ended up paying six
weeks of time so I had this other woman
move in right after I gave birth and she
looked after me for rent for six weeks
kind of thing and he's a horrible cook
that's old roommate story he amazing
human being horrible cook but then good
I'd her Cubs that she wouldn't be
someone who was in my life for that
period of time if I'd know he would've
worked he was oh good times
um but so at the very end of my
pregnancy I hadn't smoked I didn't smoke
for the three months before I conceived
and I didn't smoke for my entire
pregnancy but at the end of my pregnancy
when you're 36 weeks you're considered
turn and on my 36 - the day I went to
the doctor and I had high blood pressure
and their solution to that is to induce
at term which is 37 weeks which would
have been the next day so my family flew
out this is like a whole but my birth
story will be a whole Sunday thing you
know itself but basically they induced
me promised me that once they start
induction it they won't stop then
stopped induction three days later I'm
still after having read the paper on
blood pressure
there's no besides the fact that child's
term and it's dangerous for them all for
the maternal person carrying the baby
right to be to have a high blood
pressure they if you're not 37 weeks
they monitor you to see if you're in
preeclampsia if you have protein in your
urine if you're 37 weeks they induce you
but they induced me and then they
stopped and I had no support system now
explain support system and flown here
and flown back home and so my goal was
to get my kid to 40 weeks they were like
that's not gonna happen there's no
chance your blood pressure is high you
can't some we don't know when you're
gonna give birth but it'll be before 40
weeks i meanwhile was like no my kids
gonna cook as long as she's supposed to
cook you guys have done what you're
supposed to do in fucked
so I'm gonna and I looked up how I can
reduce blood pressure and pot was one of
the things so nine months pregnant with
my baby with I walked over to my my old
roommates house I now have no roommate
my mom's staying with me um but she has
to go home right away so we went to go
buy pot all right I think she actually
gave it to me from a few blocks away
well I'm super pregnant and I saw pot
plus two and a half three months weeks
of my pregnancy and I made it to term I
made it to the forty weeks the doctors
were like wow what did you do no idea
magic magic happens because I clearly
wasn't gonna tell them I was doing that
because it can be reason to have your
child taken away even though it's like
so you'll give me something you'll fuck
over my body you'll stop the procedure
but I can't possibly and then I didn't
smoke it at all as soon as she was born
I was just using it to keep my blood
pressure down and then there was this
what happens I had a cold she had a cold
I was like anti-drug a hundred percent
meaning like no Tylenol know anything
she had a cold and I literally nursed
her through it and then I got the colds
and I was like this sucks and I took the
Medicaid I took medication I should feel
awful in flu and I'm like I'm not
putting my kid through that from now on
she's gonna have time at all if she's
sick like it make sense to bring down
the fever it makes sense to make you as
comfortable as possible and in that
there was something like she teeth at
like 10 11 months and instead of giving
her the Tylenol I was like this doesn't
feel quite right and said I smoked pot
she got like the tiny bit my breast milk
and that seemed to bit between that and
the amber necklace it was like teething
was nothing and I still didn't smoke it
daily I didn't smoke it daily until I
think after my sir and when I stopped
bright because I was only when she was
teething but I would smoke it and then I
knew that there was legality involved
both that I smoked her pregnancy and
that I have a small child and I smoked
it so I wanted to get and I see I do
smoke it for a reason I didn't tell this
during this so I went oh I had radiation
in 2010 for my brain surgery and I was
living with the boyfriend two always
needed in the house but didn't need to
smoke it and I needed to smoke it but
not have it in the house and I went
through radiation on my brain during
that time period and I went off of pot
for that time
but that my lady radiologist oncologists
radiologists was like this is normally
when people start smoking pot and what
go off of it like are you looking for a
prescription I can give you a
prescription so then I knew I could get
a prescription but I didn't want it
during that time period and now that I
had a child I was like oh I need a
prescription if I'm gonna do this I need
it to be legal I need it to be that my
kid can't be taken away from me and so I
went through the process of getting it
legally and getting the prescription
made even though I've been you know
self-medicating with it for over a
decade at this point in time with some
with some periods off I got the the
irony is my daughter
I named her is Aurora and the company
that sells legal pot before it was legal
in Canada the place you go through for
your prescription is called Aurora as
well so I hope this stuff unlike what do
you buy i buy pot for my child
he comes with her name on it that yeah
with my various conditions it's funny
cuz I walk past before when there was
like illegal pot shops everywhere in
Vancouver but it was kind of just
decriminalized but not quite
decriminalized at the cops didn't like
you they could still charge you and
there were pot shops everywhere there
would be a list of like all of the UM
conditions that qualify you for pot
right glycome do you have this do you
have that and I would look through the
list and it was like I had you know 10
out of the 20 yep-yep-yep arthritis and
I'm yes and an anxiety and and all of
these different things I was like cool
if I I called my firts I got um a
prescription and now I have a
prescription and that was long before it
was legal and it's no bit legal about a
year and a bit I think that time bear it
up time flies smoking but but this
period of time after must have been
actually no it wouldn't have been my
second brain surgery because I remember
when I was in Brownsville my kid was
just under two years old and every time
we because I we'd have class on we had
class on Mondays and Tuesdays and then
we'd not the rest of the time so she was
so that's why I could go to school
because the only two days a week and
every weekends I would come back on
Monday
like my project pivot in I smoke Detroit
Detroit I pivoted it's basically and now
that's like my life like mmm so much a
joy don't change the world they save the
world and so it's weird because it's
both intimately tied to this thing that
is coming through me this global
cooperative and solutions cooperative
and we're gonna save the world with and
I get these epiphanies and I I think
most people do when they smoke pot
that's why they smoke it is that and yet
at the same time and I every symptom on
my every symptom of my various diagnosis
ease pot helps with like I have a lack
of appetite pot helps with that I have
trouble sleeping it helps with that I
have I don't have trouble sleeping at
all if I'm smoking pot but if I don't
then I have trouble sleeping I know
appetite of course helps reduce the pain
or rather I care less then I'm in pain
and it doesn't really help with my
anxiety but it's on the list of things
that it could it could potentially help
with anxiety and it did an ironic way
when I like went on anti-anxiety meds
had to go off of pot what it really was
on the wrong anti-anxiety meds and when
I went off of them like the tiny went
down cuz I've really been updating it
with prescriptions instead of decreasing
it was like but it's intimately tied to
what I'm doing but I'm finding this
cycle of like I've known I've been
addicted to pot for I mean my whole life
when it's been there I've smoked it when
I was living with me and it was very
clear I was like I know what it was
addicted here and yet you're the one who
needs it in the house though so it was
like him it was just a bad combination
between the two of us but it's it's he
could say no to it and I was like I just
constantly need to smoke it yes because
right now I'm struggling I'm struggling
with being in the pandemic my kids
aren't at school I use it for sensory
processing and stuff a lot so I use it
to leave my house I can't drive on it of
course so if we were gonna go do
something like car free days or going to
the community centre it's a lot easier I
can handle sights and sounds and smells
more easily if I'm stoned so I smoked
pot and we take the bus to these places
that clearly drain so this is insane
isn't isn't
option nobody's going out and doing
things but there's a lot more sensory
shit in my house right my my roommates
home all the time my kids home all the
time and there's a lot of sounds less
smells but a lot of sounds and so I
retreat and it's easier so pot it's like
how to deal with that without being
stoned he said so beeping I'm figuring
out and so I tried for the first few
weeks to try and up the I was like not
until noon for this week and they're not
till one and not till two and I got told
to and I was gonna hold it there and
then it all fell apart it's like 9 a.m.
I can smoke it right it's sometimes
known audience I think the earliest but
finding it so for the last week or so
I've definitely been during the day all
day and yesterday after getting off of
our round table I I smoked it and there
was this like Epiphany might be the
wrong word it was so I was like this is
so easy I love wind like the next GPS
coordinate is or the next piece of
advice for my guides is something so
profoundly easy then it's like why
wasn't I doing it what this can't be
that's it anyway um I smoked the potty
clean the kitchen because - one of the
things I realized that I need is a clean
house and I constantly realize this it's
not a new thing but everything to do
with spoons is a balancing act it's like
no pot isn't really the option it
doesn't seem to be that what what the
universe wants me to do nor does smoking
and also everyday that one's a little
bit harder - but that would honestly
make better balance with zero than with
what I'm doing but with cleaning my
house if I / if I click if my house is
clean then I don't have the spoons to
enjoy anyway and so it's finding the
balance of being okay with it the way it
is having a clean house gives me spoons
but cleaning my house takes them away
eating a really good diet gives me more
spoons but creating the food that gives
me that cost me spoons so it's figure
you know what's giving me more versus
what it's taking away right if I have to
spend 20 students to create a meal
that's going to give me five that's not
actually helpful so that is is what what
the balance is and pot is part of the
pod you know helps me sleep helps me eat
properly or
not eat properly but eat it helps me
actually put food in my body so it helps
with the symptoms at the same time and
hurts it hurts life in general and so
anyway the Epiphany yesterday I smoked
pot it was cleaning my my kitchen with
music on and dancing around and my kid
was out there dancing around I was like
oh if I'm gonna smoke pot earlier in the
day and not wait until be really late
hour of 2:00 p.m. I was the idea was to
get it to 60 and then see if I could not
smoke until 6:00 p.m. good that's what I
okay with that that would be my ideal is
smoking it only in the evening time but
I'm not there yet and right now if I'm
smoking during the day feeling bad about
it feeling like I failed is I know the
road to making it worse and worse as an
addiction if I feel bad my house is a
mess and it's gonna have less spoons to
clean it I have a messy house and low
spoon since it was like a bad
combination being hard on myself for how
I have to live my life it's never great
being kind of compassionate with myself
and surrendering to what is and then
slightly improving it is my path towards
improving it and so that is what I've
been doing with pot and every time I
come around on a cycle of addiction or I
won't smoke it for two weeks or I'll
figure out how to get to not smoke it
and then it will get worse every time it
has less of a stronghold on my life and
so I can see that it's like winding the
addiction down as opposed to like
winding it up but it's still here it's
still real and so what I got was if I'm
gonna smoke ignore any like today I
can't smoke it right when I get off of
here because uh-huh because I need to do
I need to put up all my videos for this
coming week and I have to something I
don't remember me Mellie said I have
some stuff to do and I can't do that
stone so I need to wait till then but
once I get stoned once I actually smoke
pot the first period of time the first
hour is going to be cleaning my house
with music on and that's something where
then I will have a more clean house
it'll never be a hundred percent clean
probably because it'll it must be a
little bit messy from the last 24 hours
even when I get it to that point but if
I intimately tie a pot smoking with
cleaning my house and I'll live in a
clean
house and feel like I've accomplished
something in which when I feel like I've
accomplished something and I'm doing
okay I have like anyone it has less
addiction in my life when I'm connected
and feel productive I have less it has
less of a stronghold other people are
like right so push it out so you can
have more of that right or connection
with people and more purpose and
actually get shit done that doesn't work
for me I don't know why it works for
other people but like forcing it out
even when like when the doctor took it
away when the doctor was like actually
you can't be on this and anti-anxiety
meds and I had to go off of it I did but
it was a lot harder and I was trying to
do once a week and it was it's I have to
be in the right place to be like this is
enough you need to go off it for two
weeks and I know I'm almost there which
is why I'm not like okay you have to not
do it in the morning because I know that
I am three or four days away from being
like you're a shit parent stop doing
this because it's always it always comes
down so like how it affects my kid and
right now it's like during the day it's
fine but at night if I've smoked it
during the day I'm a lot less patient at
night and I'm already less patient at
night even when I'm not smoking it
because of my pain and exhaustion so
groggy stoned mind with brain fog you
know the like it exasperates a lot of my
conditions when I've been smoking it all
day and again it helps me sleep which is
one of the reasons I also do it it is
like then I'll have a nap during the day
and then I'm if I just did that the naps
that didn't do it the rest of the day it
would actually be beneficial but
whatever I never really know whether
it's my addiction talking like no you
still leave me you still need me versus
actual how it how it works which is
sorry of my life how do you ever know of
something in this placebo or not was
evil but marijuana marijuana so that is
up till this point in my life 37 minutes
my marijuana story and I'm sure there oh
that was what I was gonna say I left it
out that's right I was in Australia and
was it legal there but they definitely
smoked it I mean it was like Vancouver
culture but they always smoke it with
tobacco and so does my ex or he would
smoke it tobacco is the only way I would
smoke it well before we were before we
dated we went on like a couple dates and
then we were friends for a year and a
bit and then we started dating on
Christmas Day
during the time where we were just
friends we would get together and smoke
pot and like play board games and during
that period I think I only ever smoked
it with like with him and it was to fact
it was with tobacco which is an
interesting side don't smoke tobacco
I've never been a smoker the only way I
spoke to backhoe is the one off times
for my friends really wanted to see me
smoke because it from joy I was like
fine I'm going to take a drag from it
I'm fine with that but um smoking it
with the the pot boards put in any one
it's not experience that is um it's like
it gives you a weird high right away
because of the tobacco and then the the
marijuana high kicks and after their so
it's a weird combination I get why
people do it but also then getting
addicted to tobacco it's hard to get off
of that which it's already hard enough
getting off the pot let alone make seen
it was something that has the physical
addiction and chemical addiction and
psychological addiction like all
physical is the chemical one isn't it
it's watching I'd seen Jordan Peterson
in a while but his daughter did a did a
few like two or three months ago a video
explaining that he's addicted to not
SSRIs he's addicted to one of the mental
drugs and was like but it's a it's a
what'd she say it's a chemical a
chemical addiction not a psychological
one or something and I was like how do
you how do you separate those two he's
it's not a reflection on his character
it's only the chemical imbalance it's
like and you don't think that's the same
for every other addict on the planet
it's like no those ones are are lazy and
stupid Jordan Peterson clearly isn't so
he only has this other kind of addiction
and I get it it's his daughter right
like he's but it was just the way it was
said I was like yeah he's addicted to
them his body's addicted and it's not
like it actually like when you go off of
them there's a certain percentage of the
population that can't go off of them and
their body starts shaking and they they
have to like taper off really slowly and
he's one of those people and it doesn't
there's other flaws in his personality
this isn't one of them but but their way
of explaining that is showcasing that
it's actually a flaw and everybody
accepted him so it's like no it's just
like if if you look at people with
addictions with action like the the data
and what it shows people who are
addicted to to some hardcore drugs are
people who've had a lot of trauma in
their lives are people who do a who are
empathetic people who feel pain of the
world including their own pain a need to
numb it away and that is what I've come
to realize about my addiction thank God
it's only because it is something that I
can go off of and then although because
there are times I definitely get down at
myself for it and other things and I
have had trauma in my life as everyone
has but most of my trauma that I'm
reacting to isn't actually my trauma and
so I can't heal it like I can't I can
deal with you know my parents thanking
me and not giving me love as a child
that is that is stuff I can look at and
be like right they were young and stupid
and they loves me as best they could and
I can I can't really do that for the
world's pain I can't really heal it
besides to heal it and so there is a
truth there's a truth in I'm numbing out
the pain of the world when I'm smoking
pot and also I'm strong enough to not
need to do that and so it's which one of
those I'm I'm in at the moment because
there are times where no I do feel the
pain in the world I feel the weight of
the world I'm needing to save it and
what's the one thing I can do to numb it
up and at the same time no I mean it out
means you're like I'm not moving forward
with it it's like the biggest help to
creating a world that works for everyone
it's given me a lot of the epiphanies
that have gotten you know where I am and
it also is not the most constructive
drug like my vision of the future and
diversity this is not please let's not
actually do this but like the pot
smokers come up with the ideas and like
the coke ads do them because the coke
cans like the ones with the energy I'd
like to go go go come on get things done
but not necessarily the thinking
contemplate errs and the pot smokers are
like the thinking concepts later
like but someone else is gonna need to
do it like ice at enough to join figured
how to save the world all but someone
else is gonna need to actually implement
this and there is a psychological truth
and a biological truth to that
like aside from pina pot smoker like if
I was only a pot smoker I would stop in
and save the world because I wouldn't
have my other limitations but because I
have the other limitations that I have
to have stress stress free existence
that I have I have to no mo a lot of the
pain I'm supposed to take pain
medication even though it does call it's
like so that it even if it numbs it a
bit it's helpful it's it reduces the
pain cycle I don't know the more your
body feels paying them or it's gonna
feel pain so the less it feels it's less
but it's still there you sweat don't
really like at no point is my body not
in pain so was that quite I don't know
Sunday's I'm figuring out how to do this
in the morning how to show up and do
this which is actually helping cuz one I
know I can't smoke it before this and a
lot of days tomorrow I have a 6 a.m.
appointment with somebody so tonight I
have to be in bed and I get ask me
better to certain hour and it definitely
helps me sleep at night my kid does not
help my kids sleep at night well better
which I mean I of course I'm not giving
it to her I'm taking it and then I I get
sleepy and she does not get sleepy
through osmosis of be next to me it's 10
p.m. it's time to be crazy
anyone who hasn't had kids there's this
really weird thing the kids do they get
too hungry to eat and then they're just
fucking cranky and I get it cuz I get
him at stea I'm like I'm 200 you know
what I even walk but I know my blood
sugar is low so that one I think kind of
get but they get too tired to sleep and
like let it get past that point it's my
love
you
honey dad mom we both need our house to
be clean I'm not a clean person by
nature but then I've had to step up my
cleaning after having a kid after just
having disability
whereas chicas not just like dropped
something like my my job to pick it up
you pick it up you're close or you're
the one who wants to picked up and
anyway so our house is a bit of a mess I
can the living room is set up so my dad
can do his his workouts and stay as
healthy as he can and anyway she's like
messed up the living room is like an
explosion my room is a mess but my bed
is not and so she wants to come and hang
out in here it's just the one place
that's clean I'm like clean any of the
other places I am anyway so we figured
that out because I'm going to be after
I've done my Sunday work I'm going to
smoke pot nicly for an hour and then
I'll figure that out but it's just a
little aware oh she is my favorite
person in the world and I could not have
given birth to somebody who triggers me
more mystified sounds it like on purpose
like the rest of the world is chaotic
and messy for me and and triggers me
constantly and I know that I don't make
it at fault for that because it's not
it's fault
like if somebody has a smell that
triggers me if someone's making a sound
that triggers me I don't generally don't
even ask someone to stop unless I know
them right if someone's making a
clicking sound on the bus or do it I'm
not gonna ask them to stop I just
generally don't take the bus but with
her I both have a relationship that I
can ask her to stop but also she's a kid
oh you want me to stop it
how about 10 times worse yep I gave
birth to that yep that's of course
because I couldn't handle that from
anyone else at the same time how perfect
the cheese both the person that I want
to improve my patience for and the
person who requires the most patients
and the person who's like pushing that
like who's going that is how I'm gaining
more patience it's not actually from the
world it's like from my kid who I wish I
could be infinitely pay
they clearly can't be when I'm exhausted
and tired and yet she's also entired at
that point 10:00 p.m. at night when I'm
just done when I clock out where's the
clock Oh button my shift ended
I don't want home while you're still
awake and she's in her like I clearly
need to be sleeping but I'm overly tired
now state and that is just like the
worst combination she gets overly
emotional I'm already there and it's
just like bunny heads but then she gets
in these like she's my kid and she's
stubborn okay like no I'm standing right
here until you let me in no you're not
I'm not it's not happening and because
of my spoons I do give it a lot and then
she gets that not feedback like ooh if
you're on she knows even if I cut out I
pad that if I'm like on here for this
hour that she can use it if I have
something planned that I have to go do
it's like well then I because otherwise
he'll just be interrupted every five
minutes it's been a it's been an hour
yet I was like I just need 10 more
minutes she's like 10 minutes that's a
lifetime it's like yeah I did a
seven-year-old I got it I did it it
really truly is and unfortunately she
like in the Mauryan her first thing just
like I have things I need to do
minecraft worlds I need to build and all
that and so in the morning when I'm more
on it she does nothing wants to do with
me and then as soon as I click over into
my brain not quite working and me
needing to rest and she's like I want to
do something together can we do it in
the morning
one of my brain is just like I have a
specific like maybe four hours five
hours in the morning that my brain works
better my body works better and so that
is where I concentrate my time to to do
my project of saving the world but it's
also she's my front like she's very much
my first and most important project like
she is being a parent to her is huge and
yet so I want to also have that my peak
time to be dedicated to her in my
project and making me have more peak
time because the more my house has claim
the more time that stretched on for the
more I'm eating while the more that
stretched on for when I'm looking after
my mental and physical health the more
that's that it you know goes for five to
six hours instead of and to you know
hang out and have time with my child
what
the irony of life and of course she she
wants the most time let you like I'm
sure every kid 9:00 p.m. right like like
it's bedtime
hey let's start to craft let's talk
about the meaning of the universe let's
have all those things I have told you
constantly for days that I'm not going
to tell you about right now as well I'll
tell you about them and so of course as
a parent you're like yes tell me tell me
more tell me just this thing she's seven
17 years old and I asked her about her
dreams as she has nightmares I'm like
well what are they I can help you fix
and she's like my dreams are where I
keep my secrets like that's where your
subconscious knows your secret so if I
tell you my dreams you'll know my
secrets for so many mom so I'm supposed
to don't your secrets
and second of all yes and at the same
time like who sets that I can't tell you
my dream so you'll be able to decode
them and you'll know my secrets like
okay what would add which is also ironic
is she literally cannibal and carry a
secret love secrets with her friends on
the way home be like we did this body
not anything and this not anything great
now I'm the keeper of this secret Oh
like I know her parrot I know the
parents of almost everyone she hangs out
with fairly well to know their type of
personality and at one point we weren't
co-hosting medico house in a month she's
like I really miss co-host me too me too
but she was there with her best friends
and on the way home she was talking
about Pennywise the clown from it that
she got traumatized watching a
commercial from it and sometimes pops up
on YouTube because she'll be on my
YouTube chat my my YouTube account and
then they'll advertise to me so it'll
come you know like they need to have I
want I don't fucking care if my videos
are made for children I have a child
who's watching your videos let me put it
on don't play scary stupid videos that
are erratic
look why why are you doing that don't
autoplay them please my kid also shares
this account anyway so she does not like
clowns does not like penny wise but that
she was talking about it and they were
watching it like they were watching it
on the tablet in in her friend's bedroom
there's seven and it was her friend who
was over and
knew how to get it and I think it was on
deaf I don't even know how they got it
don't think it's on that place and so
anyway I texted her dad it was like so
they were watching it just so you know
it's like not because in some families a
seven-year-old watching it wouldn't be a
big deal and so then you know that just
don't let your kid watch them over there
but I also know that this family is like
one hour of tablet time I was like your
kid was watching it with my kid that's
not it it was just that the irony of the
odd time I'd be like just so you know
what's going on it's like the background
sharing of information with parents like
don't tell your kid that I told that I
got this information for mine the
information will stop he forgot it just
to let you know what our kids are up to
this time last year I loved it I loved
it
we're often the pod story clearly well
the irony about cohousing is literally
everyone there are smokes but not
everyone the but they don't talk about
it something they don't know I do oh
well then like we went camping a year
and a half ago and I asked all the
people I know smoke it yeah including
this one guy who was like off of it for
that time period and who's off of
alcohol and pot and it was like okay
he's not doing it but I asked a few the
other people want to be older older
women was like can I have psych I'm
sorry I didn't ask you that was rude
it's like I didn't think of her as
someone who smokes at it so I didn't
invite her yeah always you're invited
anyway um oh the story so they they have
free run of cohousing there and out of
each other's houses which is one of the
reasons we're not there right now and
they're having hard times your
quarantine because I'm not really
designed to be him social distancing
well in community that's designed for
anything but social distancing what
they're making it work and they're
singing it at 6:45 and they're a lot of
people have went away if they have a
rural property they can go to family's
property they're there but east to ins't
says one of the parents they wanted the
other single parents that lives there as
dad works in a pot place he smokes pot
and they he was away and my kids best
friend was looking after their gerbils
so they had the key and my kid took we
couldn't find her anywhere we had to
leave her and her best friend her best
friends
like gone so the whole we're like are
they because they're in cohousing that's
fine they're in somebody's house but
like we don't know if they left and went
on the street and couldn't get back in
we don't we couldn't find him anywhere
and they ended up they were in this in
this house we kind of figured out went
up the ends then they came out and she
was not in trouble but she was also like
I found gummies and I ate them I'm like
do not tell me is from this person so
luckily they were like the will chisel
gummies but anyway that was not the
story um
they were like there was this mystery
and there because because there's for
like less than 40 units 2530 units in
the place and you know everyone who
lives there Stephen with someone comes
and you don't let them in you can ask
who they're visiting but you know with
their visiting the amazon person right
like you know where their house is so
you can let them and so it's someone
stands out when they don't belong there
like everyone's gonna ask you who are
you staying with who are you visiting
who are you it's very obvious when
someone doesn't belong there there's
this family who is multi-generational
who lives there so the mum and and her
husband lives together and they're they
have two kids one of whom was already
there when they got married and they
adopted boys she grew up she has two
kids and she also lives there one of her
kids is a teenager and one of them's a
little bit older than my kid and I was
eating dinner with the Grandma and
Grandpa and the teenager comes in asked
for the car keys it's going with with
grandpa gets the car keys goes and
through my kid was like there was this
person and he was in and out of people's
houses oh that's that's suspicious and
when she told me which I was this UN in
and out of and they were like solving
this mystery of this person and they
think he's stealing because he's like it
because I was I was like oh you mean his
grandmother's house and his house he
lives there you just don't see him very
often gets as a teenager but I remember
being a kid in doing that we found
diapers diapers in a neighbor's and
garbage like it was you know overflowing
and there were snipers we like had them
like paying his kidnappers not the
obvious they have a baby and or were
babysitting
like there's diapers comparable either
kidnapping children and keeping them
it's necessary it's like there's this
person who doesn't belong here
it was funny cuz they were like planning
at what to do with this intruder and
like they were telling people that there
was an intruder or people were taken
seriously like yeah he's not he's not
actually an intruder he lives here full
time he lives here so that is I'm gonna
get off now my kid can have my one clean
square surface my bed that gets made
every day the rest of my room is not
clean and it's on the list today to
clean so that was my marijuana world
that was my story of my marijuana um
this is nothing to do with saving the
world to get everything stay with it I'm
coming on everyday at 8:30 to 9:30 in
the morning I still don't quite know why
but sticking it out cuz this is what I
was told to do and there is it is moving
forward on Wednesdays we do the solution
raising this Wednesday is going to be on
energy and how we need energy in the
world and what we're currently doing for
what we could do as an adjacent possible
with 10,000 people and $100,000 and
we're also setting up another solution
raising on game be mapping from
yesterday's round table so that is what
I'm doing absolution raising and that is
I have to go and make today Sunday so
I'm making all of the videos for this
coming week updating my spreadsheet
putting them on the the knack tool which
I teach you last week's I couldn't
figure it out and then then I get a
smoke leave my house and hope like it's
a little bit cleaner my kid can go in
here and hang out now that I'm off of
here so I will see you all tomorrow I
will be just getting off of a okay so
not just getting up I have a 6 a.m.
phone call in three minutes until 10:00
until 7:00 and then I'll be here at 8:30
so an hour to half later so I guess it
won't be coming right off even have time
to have a downtime maybe have a second
coffee tomorrow and Tuesday idea cafe
from the edgy cafe channel I'll be here
as well and then Wednesday April did the
solution race
on energy live here with other people
joining and this might be the last week
on Fridays I do life coaching this is
just something to do that made sense
with the five questions Fridays
dedicated to the five questions right
now that looks like life coaching which
doesn't seem to this is a very eclectic
collective might not be the word channel
and do a lot of different things on it
um and so maybe that's it and it doesn't
resonate with that with this group the
same people who want to watch me ramble
on about how I'm saving the world for an
hour also maybe not the ones for like oh
gee but this Friday will be the last one
will be doing the the brain walk one
it's the download the kick so you have
the brain walk printed out and then you
can which will be available today later
later putting that the two that will be
up on this channel will be the solution
raising in the Friday life coaching
I'm the ones I do in the morning I just
put up the morning on because it's just
easier you can usually come in join me
on these broadcasts there's a link in
the description except for solution
raising which if you want to participate
you can get in contact with me come
participate but it's an hour long so
it's not something you can pop in and
pop motive and the idea Cafe same thing
they're both hour-long conversation so
you're welcome to come and join them but
you can't just join the last minute um
life coaching you can call someone tried
on Friday was a little bit a bit proud
actually um but I will see you all
tomorrow
take care